Chase Murtaugh

Greater Philadelphia



chasemurtaugh@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/chase-murtaugh-71ba82109

Summary

I was trained through Penn University in full-stack web development. Experienced in HTML, CSS, jQuery, JSON, React, MongoDB. Built numerous projects throughout the course of my training. Both solo and with a team. Learned both leadership and how teamwork drives development in the field. Experienced with trello and kanban to increase communication, management and problem solving in web projects.

Three years working with numerous EMR softwares in the Emergency department at Inspira Medical Center for Scribe America.

I then worked as a Scribe Ambassador for Scribe America at sites around the country introducing and developing scribe programs to numerous specialties and clinics. Successfully integrated every client into our system and set them up for long-term partnership with Scribe America.

3.7 GPA, 3.5 Science GPA.

Experience



Scribe

ScribeAmerica Apr 2017 - Present (4 years 6 months +)



Sales Associate

K Mart Stores Nov 2014 - Aug 2015 (10 months)

Education



Clemson University

Bachelor of Science (BS), Industrial and Organizational Psychology 2016 - 2019



Pace University

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Pre-Medicine/Pre-Medical Studies 2015 - 2016



West Deptford High School

High School Graduate 2011 - 2015

Skills

Problem Solving • Customer Service • Social Media • Information Technology • American History • Event Planning • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • HTML • jQuery

Honors & Awards

Living the Ritual - Chi Psi Fraternity

May 2019

Awarded to me by the national fraternity for leading Chi Psi of Clemson to be the first fraternity on campus to work with local-area charities and foundations.